[Music]
life is a journey filled with Beautiful
Moments and shared laughter but
uncertainties arrive unannounced and as
your committed Insurance partner we
stand by you offering support when you
need it the
most you can protect your loved ones
tomorrow with a few right steps today
always keep your nominee informed about
the policy details and steps to file a
claim share correct and complete
information in the application form when
you purchase the
policy review the copy of the
application form sent in your welcome
kit in case of any changes reach out to
us for
assistance now let's understand the
simple steps to file an insurance claim
in case of any unforeseen event your
nominee can approach any of our touch
points to file a claim visit the nearest
icic credential Branch there would be
claims related assistance provided on
priority visit our website for online
submission of the claim and documents
corer the claim related documents to our
claim Care office keeping the
convenience of your nominee first we
also arrange for a doorstep document
pickup to initiate the claim process the
nominee must provide mandatory documents
that include claimant statement form
death certificate of the life assured
kyc of the nominee that is current
address and ID proof recent photo and
pan card cancelled check bank account
statement or a passbook of the nominees
bank account additional documents may be
required such as Medical Hospital
records or police records depending on
the type of death to enable faster claim
processing please visit the claim
section on our website for more details
on
documentation once all documents are
submitted a unique claim ID will be
shared with the Nomine via email or SMS
the claim status can be tracked real
time on our website by using this claim
ID the nominee will also be updated at
every stage of claim processing Via SMS
email letters and WhatsApp we understand
the urgency during such challenging
times therefore we ensure faster
processing of claims we have decisioned
99.04% of claims in financial year 2023
within the regulatory
timelines at ICICI credential life
insurance we believe that standing by
you and your loved ones and ensuring a
smooth claim settlement is the ultimate
service we can
provide
[Music]